A Guide to the William and Flora Hewlett Foundation records FA1501
Rockefeller Archive Center
- Oral History Project, 1995-2004; 5; 1.52 Cubic Feet 4 letter document boxes
  - Background Materials, 1995-2004; 2
    - Correspondence - Toben, 1999-2001 (Box 13, Folder 134)
    - Child Development Project - Dyke Brown Interview, 1998-2000 (Box 13, Folder 135)
    - Neighborhood Improvement - Executive Summary: Implementation of the Regional Development and CED Project, 1990 January 17 (Box 13, Folder 136)
    - Conflict Resolution - Robert A. Baruch Bush Report and Commentary, 1995-1999 (Box 13, Folder 137)
    - Interviews - James Hewlett, Walter Hewlett, Mary Jaffe (Box 13)
- Annual Reports, 1966-2008; 6; 2.28 Cubic Feet 6 letter document boxes
  - 1966-1977 (Box 13, Folder 138-139)
  - 1978-1985 (Box 14, Folder 140-147)
  - 1986-1992 (Box 15, Folder 148-154)
  - 1993-1999 (Box 16, Folder 155-161)
  - 2000-2005 (Box 17, Folder 162-167)
  - 2006-2008 (Box 18, Folder 168-169)
- Board of Directors Meeting Dockets, 2000-2014; 7; 4.94 Cubic Feet 13 letter document boxes
  Meeting dockets containing quarterly reports on each program area. Program areas include: conflict resolution, education, environment, global development, family and community development, performing arts, population, US-Latin American relations, and special projects.
  - 2000 July 14-17 (Box 18, Folder 170)
  - 2000 October 15-16 (Box 18, Folder 171)
  - 2001 February 11-12 (Box 18, Folder 172-173)
  - 2001 October 14-15 (Box 19, Folder 174)
  - Carolyn Provost, 2002 January 27-28 (Box 19, Folder 175)
  - 2002 April 14-15 (Box 19, Folder 176)
  - 2002 July 14-15 (Box 19, Folder 177)
  - Carolyn Provost, 2002 October 20-21 (Box 19, Folder 178)
    Includes building dedication.
  - John McGuirk, 2003 January 12-13 (Box 20, Folder 179)
  - John McGuirk, 2003 April 13-14 (Box 20, Folder 180)
  - John McGuirk, 2003 July 13-14 (Box 20, Folder 181)
  - John McGuirk, 2003 October 19-20 (Box 20, Folder 182)
  - John McGuirk, 2004 January 25-26 (Box 20, Folder 183)
  - John McGuirk, 2004 April 4-5 (Box 21, Folder 184)
  - Carolyn Provost, 2004 July 11-12 (Box 21, Folder 185)
  - Carolyn Provost, 2004 October 24-25 (Box 21, Folder 186-187)
  - John McGuirk, 2005 February 27-28 (Box 21, Folder 188)
  - Carolyn Provost, 2005 June 19-20 (Box 21, Folder 189)
  - Carolyn Provost, 2005 September 8-10 (Box 22, Folder 190)
  - 2005 October 16-17 (Box 22, Folder 191-192)
  - Linda Clayton, 2005 October 16-17 (Box 30, Folder 228-229)
  - Nancy Strausser, 2006 February 26-27 (Box 22, Folder 193)
  - Jean McCall, 2006 June 18-19 (Box 22, Folder 194)
  - 2006 October 15-16 (Box 30, Folder 230-231)
  - Nancy Strausser, 2006 October 15-16 (Box 23, Folder 195-196)
  - Nancy Strausser, 2007 February 25-26 (Box 23, Folder 197)
  - Jean McCall, 2007 November 18-19 (Box 23, Folder 198)
  - Nancy Strausser, 2008 March 16-17 (Box 23, Folder 199)
  - Carolyn Provost, 2008 July 20-21 (Box 24, Folder 200)
  - Megan Mermis, 2008 September 9-12 (Box 24, Folder 201)
  - Nancy Strausser, 2008 November 16-17 (Box 24, Folder 202)
  - Nancy Strausser, 2009 March 29-30 (Box 24, Folder 203)
  - Megan Mermis, 2009 March 29-30 (Box 25, Folder 204)
  - Nancy Strausser, 2009 July 19-20 (Box 25, Folder 205)
  - Retreat - Megan Mermis, 2009 September 15-17 (Box 25, Folder 206)
  - Jean McCall, 2009 November 15-16 (Box 25, Folder 207)
  - Megan Mermis, 2010 March 21-22 (Box 26, Folder 208)
  - Connie Bassett, 2010 March 21-22 (Box 26, Folder 209)
  - Connie Bassett, 2010 July 18-19 (Box 26, Folder 210)
  - Megan Mermis, 2010 September 13-15 (Box 26, Folder 211)
  - Nancy Strausser, 2010 November 14-15 (Box 26, Folder 212)
  - 2010 November 14-15 (Box 27, Folder 213)
  - Megan Mermis, 2011 March 20-21 (Box 27, Folder 214)
  - 2011 July 17-18 (Box 27, Folder 215)
  - Nancy Strausser, 2011 November 13-14 (Box 27, Folder 216)
  - Eric Brown, 2011 November 13-14 (Box 28, Folder 217-218)
  - Megan Mermis, 2012 March 18-19 (Box 28, Folder 219)
  - Sarah Singh, 2012 July 15-16 (Box 28, Folder 220)
  - Sarah Singh, 2012 September 10-13 (Box 28, Folder 221)
  - Family Version, 2012 September 10-13 (Box 28, Folder 222)
  - Library, 2013 March 17-18 (Box 28, Folder 223)
  - Jon Jeter, 2013 July 21-22 (Box 29, Folder 224)
  - Jon Jeter, 2013 November 10-11 (Box 29, Folder 225)
  - Communications, 2014 March 16-17 (Box 29, Folder 226)
  - Communications, 2014 July 13-14 (Box 29, Folder 227)
- Grant Products, 1999-2012; 8; 10.51 Cubic Feet 8 record storage boxes
  Gaps in numbers due to electronic only copies.
  - Children and Youth, 2005; 1
    - CH-1 On Your Own Without A Net: The Transition to Adulthood for Vulnerable Populations - Osgood, Foster, Flanagan (2002-8268), 2005 (Box 31, Folder 232)
  - Education, 1999-2012; 2
    - E-1 Passing the Torch: Strategies for Innovation in Community College ESL, Executive Summary - Chrisman, Crandall (2004-441), 2007 (Box 31, Folder 233)
    - E-2 The Cleveland Literacy System: A Comprehensive Approach to Changing Instructional Practice - Williams (2004-5017), 2005 (Box 31, Folder 234)
    - E-3 Using Student-Assessment Results to Improve Instruction: Lessons from a Workshop - Murnane, Sharkey, Boudett (2001-7090), 2005 (Box 31, Folder 235)
    - E-4 The "Data Wise" Improvement Process: Eight Steps for Using Test Data to Improve Teaching and Learning - Boudett, City, Murnane (2001-7090), 2006 (Box 31, Folder 236)
    - E-5 Teaching Educators How to Use Student Assessment Data to Improve Instruction - Boudett, Murnane, City (2001 -7090), 2005 (Box 31, Folder 237)
    - E-6 Tough Choices in Designing a Formative Assessment System - Sharkey, Murnane (2001-7090), 2006 (Box 31, Folder 238)
    - E-7 Inquiry at Different Organizational Levels: Teachers as Reflective Practitioners - Ramirez (2004-4219), 2006 January (Box 31, Folder 239)
    - E-7 Data-Driven Instruction: A View from the Bottom Up - Young (2004-4219), 2005 April (Box 31, Folder 240)
    - E-8 The Coach's Role as a Boundary Spanner: Brokering Information and Building Legitimacy - Coggins (2004-4219), 2004 April (Box 31, Folder 241)
    - E-9 Improving Instructional Capacity through School-Based Reform Coaches - Coggins, Stoddard, Cutler (2004-4219), 2003 April (Box 31, Folder 242)
    - E-10 Towards Evidence-Based Instructional Practice - Young (2004-4219), 2004 November (Box 31, Folder 243)
    - E-11 Coaching as a Districtwide Reform Strategy - Coggins (2004-4219), 2004 October (Box 31, Folder 244)
    - E-12 Diffusion of Instructional Innovations in Schools: The Case of Knowledge for Teaching Reading to English Language Learners - Ramirez (2004-4219), 2005 March (Box 31, Folder 245)
    - E-13 Teachers' Use of Data: Embedded Contexts and Instructional Logics - Young (2004-4219), 2005 September (Box 31, Folder 246)
    - E-14 Passing the Torch: Strategies for Innovation in Community College ESL - Chrisman, Crandall (2004-4441), 2007 (Box 31, Folder 247)
    - E-15 California Community Colleges Struggle to Meet the Challenges of the State's Underprepared Workforce - California Tomorrow (2003-9029), 2007 (Box 31, Folder 248)
    - E-16 Rules of the Game: How State Policy Creates Barriers to Degree Completion and Impedes Student Success in the California Community Colleges - Shulock, Moore (2005-6787), 2007 February (Box 31, Folder 249)
    - E-17 Can California Import Enough College Graduates to Meet Workforce Needs? - Johnson, Reed (2006-8194), 2007 (Box 31, Folder 250)
    - E-18 California Community Colleges: Making Them Stronger and More Affordable - Zumeta, Frankle (2006-7724), 2007 (Box 31, Folder 251)
    - E-23 The Role of Districts in Fostering Instructional Improvement: Lessons from Three Urban Districts Partnered with the Institute for Learning - Marsh, Kerr, Ikemoto (2002-7991), 2005 (Box 31, Folder 252)
    - E-24 An International Episode - James, The Internet Archive: The Internet Bookmobile (2003-9312), 2005 (Box 31, Folder 253)
    - E-25 Old Christmas - Irving, The Internet Archive: The Internet Bookmobile (2003-9312), 2005 (Box 31, Folder 254)
    - E-26 From Blueprint to Reality: San Diego's Education Reforms - Betts, Zau, King (2003-8426), 2005 (Box 31, Folder 255)
    - E-27 Basic Education Online: Identifying High-Quality Developmental Education and ESOL Courses for the Open-Content Environment - League for Innovation in the Community College (2004-5012), 2005 (Box 31, Folder 256)
    - E-28 A Difficult Balance: Incentives and Quality Control in Alternative Certification Programs - Johnson, Birkeland, Peske (2002-7178), 2005 (Box 31, Folder 257)
    - E-29 The District Role in Instructional Improvement: A Case Study of High School Reform in San Diego City Schools - Husbands (2002-8322), 2005 September (Box 31, Folder 258)
    - E-35 Toward a K-20 Student Unit Record Data System for California - Vernez, Krop, Vuollo (2006-8637), 2008 (Box 31, Folder 259)
    - E-36 Answering the Question that Matters Most: Has Student Achievement Increased Since No Child Left Behind? - Center on Education Policy (2006-7911), 2007 (Box 31, Folder 260)
    - E-37 Torchlights in ESL: Five Community Profiles - Zachry, Dibble, Seymour (2004-4441), 2007 (Box 31, Folder 261)
    - E-40 Students First: Renewing Hope for California's Future - Governor's Committee on Education Excellence (2006-9108), 2007 November (Box 31, Folder 262)
    - E-41 Students First: Renewing Hope for California's Future, Technical Report - Governor's Committee on Education Excellence (2006-9108), 2007 November (Box 31, Folder 263)
    - E-42 Answering the Knock of Opportunity: Addressing the Data Needs for California's English Learners - Perez (2006-8421), 2008 February (Box 31, Folder 264)
    - E-43 Funding Formulas for California Schools: Simulations and Supporting Data - Rose, Sengupta, Sonstelie, 2008 January (Box 31, Folder 265)
    - E-43 Report to the Hewlett Foundation - Narrative, Work Plan and Progress, Financials, CAL-PASS Strategic Plan - California Partnership for Achieving Student Success (2005-7397), 2007 (Box 31, Folder 266)
    - E-44 The Need for Adequate Resources for At-Risk Children - Allgood (2003-9099), 2006 August (Box 31, Folder 267)
    - E-45 Invest in Success: How Finance Policy Can Increase Student Success at California's Community Colleges - Shulock, Moore (2005-6787), 2007 October (Box 31, Folder 268)
    - E-51 California's K-12 Public Schools: How Are They Doing? - Carroll, Krop, Arkes (2003-9643), 2005 (Box 32, Folder 269)
    - E-55 Choosing Better Schools: A Report on Student Transfers under the No Child Left Behind Act - Brown, Citizen's Commission on Civil Rights (2002-8440), 2004 (Box 32, Folder 270)
    - E-60 Report to the Hewlett Foundation on Development of Strategic Plan for CAL-PASS - Phillips, 2007 December (Box 32, Folder 271)
    - E-66 Opening Doors: Getting Back on Track: Effects of a Community College Program for Probationary Students - Scrivener, Sommo, Collado (2006-7928), 2009 April (Box 32, Folder 272)
    - E-68 The Benefits to Taxpayers from Increases in Students' Education Attainment - Carroll, Erkut (2005-6208), 2009 (Box 32, Folder 273)
    - E-83 Promising Practices for Middle School English Learners - Walqui (2007-8567), 2009 September (Box 32, Folder 274)
    - E-84 Policies and Practices to Improve Student Preparation and Success - Bueschel, Venezia (2006-7913), 2009 (Box 32, Folder 275)
    - E-90 Using Student Data to Improve Teaching and Learning: Findings from an Evaluation of the Formative Assessments of Student Thinking in Reading (FAST-R) Program in Boston Elementary Schools - Quint, Sepanik, Smith (2006-8569), 2008 (Box 32, Folder 276)
    - E-91 Educating California: Choices for the Future - Johnson (2007-1419), 2009 (Box 32, Folder 277)
    - E-115 Ten-Year Trends in California's Dropout and Graduate Rates - Rumberger, 2009 August (Box 32, Folder 278)
    - E-116 Ethnic and Gender Difference in California High School Graduation Rates - Rumberger, Rotermund (2009-3973), 2009 March (Box 32, Folder 279)
    - E-117 High School Dropouts and the Economic Losses from Juvenile Crime in California - Belfield, Levin (2009-3973), 2009 September (Box 32, Folder 280)
    - E-119 Closing the Achievement Gap: Report of Superintendent Jack O'Connell's California P-16 Council - California Department of Education (2007-1413), 2008 January (Box 32, Folder 281)
    - E-229 A California Education Policy Convening: Getting from Facts to Policy - EdSource (2007-1414), 2007 October 19 (Box 32, Folder 282)
    - E-230 School Resources and Academic Standards in California: Lessons from the Schoolhouse - Rose, Sonstelie, Reinhard (2001-6649), 2006 (Box 32, Folder 283)
    - E-231 School Budgets and Student Achievement in California: The Principal's Perspective - Rose, Sonstelie, Richardson (2001-6649), 2004 (Box 32, Folder 284)
    - E-232 High Expectations, Modest Means: The Challenge Facing California's Public Schools - Rose, Sonstelie, Reinhard (2001-6649), 2003 (Box 32, Folder 285)
    - E-233 Californians and Education - PPIC Statewide Survey (2005-5652), 2007 (Box 32, Folder 286)
    - E-236 Getting Down to Facts: School Finance and Governance in California - Loeb, Bryk, Hanushek (2005-6237), 2007 March (Box 32, Folder 287)
    - E-236B Getting Down to Facts Conference (2005-6237), 2007 (Box 32, Folder 288)
    - E-235 First to Worst - Learning Matters (2002-7864), 2004 (Box T1)
      Access copy currently unavailable. Please contact a RAC archivist for further instruction.
    - E-235D First to Worst - Trailer Only (2002-7864) (Box 32)
    - E-237 The Next Big Test - Washington Monthly (2011-6429), 2012 (Box 32, Folder 289)
    - E-246 Teaching and California's Future: The Status of the Teaching Profession: Research Findings and Policy Recommendations - Center for the Future of Teaching and Learning (1998-2274), 1999 (Box 32, Folder 290)
    - E-247 California's Teaching Force: Key Issues and Trends - Guha, Campbell, Humphrey (2000-4721), 2006 (Box 32, Folder 291)
    - E-248 Dissemination of Findings and Recommendations: Promising Practices for Middle School English Learners in California - Walqui (2010-5480), 2011 November (Box 32, Folder 292)
    - E-249 Tough Liberal: Albert Shanker and the Battles over Schools, Unions, Race, and Democracy - Kahlenberg (2002-8436), 2007 (Box 32, Folder 293)
    - E-250 The Status of the Teaching Profession - Wechsler, Tiffany-Morales, Campbell (2000-4721), 2007 (Box 32, Folder 294)
    - E-251 The Status of the Teaching Profession - Shields, Humphrey, Wechsler (2000-4721), 2001 (Box 32, Folder 295)
    - E-252 The Status of the Teaching Profession: An Update to the Teaching and California's Future Task Force - Shields, Esch, Humphrey (1998-2274), 2000 (Box 32, Folder 296)
    - E-330 Class and Schools: Using Social, Economic, and Educational Reform to Close the Black-White Achievement Gap - Rothstein (2003-9099), 2004 (Box 32, Folder 297)
    - E-331 Legal Report: Analysis of California and Federal Laws Governing Release of Educational Data to Researchers - Greene, Perkins (2006-8260), 2007 October 12 (Box 32, Folder 298)
    - E-332 Learning from Student Assessment Results: Lessons for New York State - Murnane, Sharkey (2001-7090), 2004 March (Box 32, Folder 299)
    - E-335 Districtwide Strategies to Promote Data Use for Instructional Improvement - Kerr, Marsh, Ikemoto (2002-7991), 2005 April (Box 32, Folder 300)
    - E-337 Learning Matters: Promo (2007-1061) (Box 32)
      Researchers interested in accessing digital media (floppy disks, CDs, DVDs, etc.) in this collection must use an access surrogate. The original items may not be accessed because of preservation concerns. Access copy currently unavailable. Please contact a RAC archivist for further instruction.
    - E-338 Recession's Effects Batter New York's School District - NewsHour with Jim Lehrer (2007-1061), 2009 (Box 32)
    - E-339 Higher Ed, Higher Costs (featuring programs: Paying for College, Drowning in Debt, The Costs of Colleges, and four related podcasts) - NewsHour with Jim Lehrer (2007-1061), 2009 (Box 32)
    - E-340 Leadership: A Challenging Course: New Leaders Trying to Fix Urban School Systems in Deep Trouble, Paul Vallas, New Orleans - NewsHour with Jim Lehrer (2007-1061), 2008 (Box 32)
    - E-341 Leadership: A Challenging Course: New Leaders Trying to Fix Urban School Systems in Deep Trouble, Michelle Rhee, Washington, D.C. - NewsHour with Jim Lehrer (2007-1061), 2008 (Box 32)
    - E-342 Leadership: A Challenging Course: New Leaders Trying to Fix Urban School Systems in Deep Trouble, Year Two: Episode 1 - NewsHour with Jim Lehrer (2007-1061), 2009 (Box 32)
    - E-343 Leadership: A Challenging Course: New Leaders Trying to Fix Urban School Systems in Deep Trouble, Year Two: Episodes 7, 8, 9 and Podcasts - NewsHour with Jim Lehrer (2007-1061), 2009 (Box 32)
    - E-344 When School is Home - NewsHour with Jim Lehrer (2007-1061), 2009 (Box 32)
    - E-354 Engineering with a Human Touch - Humanitarian Engineering Program, Colorado School of Mines (2003-8446), 2008 (Box 32)
  - Environment, 1999-2005; 3
    - EN-3 Volume 1: Pu'u Anahulu and Pu'u Wa'awa'a (napu'u), at kekaha-Kona, Hawai' I: A Report on Archival-Historical Documentary Research, and Oral History Interviews - Maly (99-4352), 1999 (Box 33, Folder 301)
    - EN-3 Volume 2: Pu'u Anahulu and Pu'u Wa'awa'a (napu'u), at kekaha-Kona, Hawai' I: Oral History Interviews - Maly (99-4352), 1999 (Box 33, Folder 302-304)
    - EN-16 Ending the Energy Stalemate: A Bipartisan Strategy to Meet America's Energy Challenges - National Commission on Energy Policy (2002-8102), 2004 December (Box 33, Folder 305)
    - EN-21 No Reason to Wait: The Benefits of Greenhouse Gas Reduction in Sao Paulo and California (2005-6993) (Box 33, Folder 306)
    - EN-22 Assessing Natural Gas and Oil Resources: An Example of a New Approach in the Greater Green River Basin - LaTourrette, Bernstein, Hanson (2002-8056), 2003 (Box 33, Folder 307)
  - Global Development, 2002-2012; 4
    - GD-1 Healthy Food, Farms & Families - Bread for the World Institute (2006-8678), 2007 (Box 33, Folder 308)
    - GD-5 Growth Report: Strategies for Sustained Growth and Inclusive Development - Commission on Growth and Development (2006-7642), 2008 (Box 33, Folder 309)
    - GD-6 The Role of Institutions in Growth and Development - Acemoglu, Robinson (2006-7642), 2008 (Box 33, Folder 310)
    - GD-7 Finance, Financial Sector Policies, and Long-Run Growth - Demirguc-Kunt, Levine (2006-7642), 2008 (Box 33, Folder 311)
    - GD-8 Cities: Engines of Growth and Prosperity for Developing Countries? - Duranton (2006-7642), 2008 (Box 33, Folder 312)
    - GD-9 Housing Policy in Developing Countries: The Importance of Informal Economy - Arnott (2006-7642), 2008 (Box 33, Folder 313)
    - GD-10 Economic Growth in Egypt: Impediments and Constraints (1974-2004) - El Beblawi (2006-7642), 2008 (Box 33, Folder 314)
    - GD-11 Spatial Inequality and Economic Development: Theories, Facts, and Policies - Kim (2006-7642), 2008 (Box 33, Folder 315)
    - GD-12 Leadership, Policy Making, and Economic Growth in African Countries: The Case of Nigeria - Iyoha (2006-7642), 2008 (Box 33, Folder 316)
    - GD-13 Urbanization, Agglomeration, and Economic Development - Quigley (2006-7642), 2008 (Box 33, Folder 317)
    - GD-14 Perspective on Growth: A Political-Economy Framework, Lessons for the Singapore Experience - Ying, Eng, Robinson (2006-7642), 2008 (Box 33, Folder 318)
    - GD-15 Exchange Rate Economics - Williamson (2006-7642), 2008 (Box 33, Folder 319)
    - GD-16 Normalizing Industrial Policy - Rodrik (2006-7642), 2008 (Box 33, Folder 320)
    - GD-17 The Real Exchange Rate and Economic Growth - Eichengreen (2006-7642), 2008 (Box 33, Folder 321)
    - GD-18 Globalization, Growth, and Distribution: Framing the Questions - Kanbur (2006-7642), 2008 (Box 33, Folder 322)
    - GD-19 Growth Strategies and Dynamics: Insights from Country Experiences - El-Erian, Spence (2006-7642), 2008 (Box 33, Folder 323)
    - GD-20 Political Competition, Policy Making, and the Quality of Public Policies in Costa Rica - Lehoucq (2006-7642), 2008 (Box 33, Folder 324)
    - GD-21 Leadership for Growth, Development, and Poverty Reduction: an African Viewpoint and Experience - Mkapa (2006-7642), 2008 (Box 33, Folder 325)
    - GD-22 Growth Strategies for Africa - Collier (2006-7642), 2008 (Box 33, Folder 326)
    - GD-25 Islam: Governance, Ideology and U.S. Policy for the New Administration and the New Congress - Clark (2006-8599), 2009 February 14-20 (Box 33, Folder 327)
    - GD-26 Energy Security and Climate Change: Policy Challenges for the New Administration and the New Congress - Clark (2006-8599), 2009 April 4-10 (Box 33, Folder 328)
    - GD-27 Political Islam: Policy Challenges for the New Administration and the New Congress - Clark (2006-8599), 2009 May 26-June 1 (Box 33, Folder 329)
    - GD-28 Improving "No Child Left Behind": Linking World-Class Education Standards to America's Economic Recovery - Clark (2006-8599), 2009 August 17-22 (Box 33, Folder 330)
    - GD-38 WTO Disciplines on Agricultural Support: Seeking a Fair Basis for Trade - Orden, Blandford, Josling (2006-7863), 2011 (Box 33, Folder 331)
    - GD-39 Globalization, Poverty, and Inequality - Collins, Graham (2004-5006) (Box 33, Folder 332)
    - GD-40 Agricultural Commodities, Trade and Sustainable Development - Lines (2004-5006), 2005 (Box 33, Folder 333)
    - GD-41 Trade Development-Poverty Linkage: Reflections from Selected Asian and Sub-Saharan African Countries - Razzaque, Raihan (2008-1887) (Box 33, Folder 334)
    - GD-42 Towards More Inclusive Trade Policy Making: Process and Role of Stakeholders in Select African Countries (2008-1887), 2009 (Box 33, Folder 335)
    - GD-43 How does Trade Lead to Development and Poverty Reduction? Evidence from the Field (2008-1888) (Box 33, Folder 336)
    - GD-44 Making Aid Work - Banerjee (2006-8224), 2007 (Box 33, Folder 337)
    - GD-45 Self-Enforcing Trade: Developing Countries and WTO Dispute Settlement - Bown (2008-2026), 2009 (Box 34, Folder 338)
    - GD-46 Brazil in the Global Economy: Measuring the Gains for Trade - Polaski, de Souza Ferreira Filho, Berg (2005-6795), 2009 (Box 34, Folder 339)
    - GD-47 Sustainable Bioenergy Development in UEMOA Member Countries - West African Economic and Monetary Union (2003-9453), 2008 (Box 34, Folder 340)
    - GD-48 Monetization of Food Aid: Reconsidering U.S. Policy and Practice - Simmons (2003-9453), 2009 (Box 34, Folder 341)
    - GD-49 Make Trade Fair - Oxfam (2005-6239), undated (Box 34, Folder 342)
    - GD-50 Fields of Gold: Lifting the Veil on Europe's Farm Subsidies (2008-2775), 2010 (Box 34)
    - GD-51 Towards an African Green Revolution: Report and Recommendations from High-Level Meetings at the Salzburg Global Seminar - Yuksel (2008-2777) (Box 34, Folder 343)
    - GD-52 Supporting Africa's Strategy for Reducing Rural Poverty: U.S. Agricultural Development Assistance, 2005-2008 - Taylor, Shiferaw (2006-8677), 2009 (Box 34, Folder 344)
    - GD-53 American Interests in South Asia: Building Grand Strategy in Afghanistan, Pakistan, and India - Scowcroft, Burns, Price (2010-6000), 2011 (Box 34, Folder 345)
    - GD-56 Setting Up a Modern Macroeconomic Policy Framework in Brazil, 1993-2004 - Werneck (2006-7642), 2009 (Box 34, Folder 346)
    - GD-57 Real Exchange Rates, Saving, and Growth: Is There a Link? - Montiel, Serven (2006-7642), 2009 (Box 34, Folder 347)
    - GD-58 Avenues for Export Diversification: Issues for Low-Income Countries - Brenton, Newfarmer, Walkenhorst (2006-7642), 2009 (Box 34, Folder 348)
    - GD-59 Macroeconomic Policy: Does it Matter for Growth? The Role of Volatility - Fatas, Mihov (2006-7642), 2009 (Box 34, Folder 349)
    - GD-60 Current Debates on Infrastructure Policy - Estache, Fay (2006-7642), 2009 (Box 34, Folder 350)